Finding Aid for the Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo, 2008
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Roberto Morales, June 2008, IV.; 1 CD-ROM (33 image files in TIFF format)
  - Composer Roberto Morales performing his work, Historia de Culebras, in front of a projected film, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Roberto Morales.jpg (Image-file cd04-22)
  - Composer Roberto Morales at the piano, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Roberto Morales.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200804-23 (Image-file cd04-23)
  - Conductor James Avery with composer Roberto Morales, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Robert Morales composer-James Avery conductor.tif (Image-file cd04-24)
  - Composer Roberto Morales performing his work, Historia de Culebras, in front of a projected film, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Roberto Morales Historia de Culebras.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200804-25 (Image-file cd04-25)
  - Composer Roberto Morales with conductor James Avery, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Roberto Morales James Avery==.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200804-26 (Image-file cd04-26)
  - James Avery conducting rehearsal of Roberto Morales's work, Remembrance, with Eun Ju Kim, piano, Martina Roth, flute, Sven Kestel, double bass, Tom Kolor (center) and Pascal Pons (left), percussion, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Roberto Morales REMEMBRENCE 08.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200804-27 (Image-file cd04-27)
  - James Avery conducting rehearsal of Roberto Morales's work, Remembrance, with Eun Ju Kim, piano, Martina Roth, flute, Sven Kestel, double bass, Tom Kolor (left) and Pascal Pons (right), percussion, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Roberto Morales Remembrance.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200804-28 (Image-file cd04-28)
  - James Avery conducting rehearsal of Roberto Morales's work, Remembrance, with Eun Ju Kim, piano, Martina Roth, flute, Sven Kestel, double bass, Tom Kolor (center) and Pascal Pons (left), percussion, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Roberto Morales Remembrence rehearsal-.tif (Image-file cd04-29)
  - James Avery conducting rehearsal of Roberto Morales's work, Remembrance, with Eun Ju Kim, piano, Martina Roth, flute, Sven Kestel, double bass, Tom Kolor (left) and Pascal Pons (right), percussion, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Roberto Morales rehearsal.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200804-30 (Image-file cd04-30)
  - James Avery conducting rehearsal of Roberto Morales's work, Remembrance, with Eun Ju Kim, piano, Martina Roth, flute, Sven Kestel, double bass, Tom Kolor (left) and Pascal Pons (right), percussion, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Roberto Morales rehearsal=.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200804-31 (Image-file cd04-31)
  - Composer Roberto Morales with student composer, Tom Stoll, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Roberto Morales with student composer.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200804-32 (Image-file cd04-32)
  - Composer Roberto Morales with student composer, Tom Stoll, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Roberto Morales with student composer=.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200804-33 (Image-file cd04-33)
- Morton Subotnick, June 2008, V.; 1 CD-ROM (8 image files in TIFF format)
  - Composer Morton Subotnick, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: composer Morton Sobotnik.tif (Image-file cd05-01)
  - Composer Morton Subotnick during lecture, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: composer. Charles Sobotnik lecture.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200805-02 (Image-file cd05-02)
  - Composer Morton Subotnick, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: June in Buffalo 09 061.jpg (Image-file cd05-03)
  - Composer Morton Subotnick during masterclass with students Asha Srinivasan and Tsai-Yun Huang, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: masterclass with Robert Subotnik.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200805-04 (Image-file cd05-04)
  - Composer Morton Subotnick during lecture, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Morton Sobotnik Lecture.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200805-05 (Image-file cd05-05)
  - Composer Morton Subotnick during lecture, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Morton Subotnik composer---=.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200805-06 (Image-file cd05-06)
  - Composer Morton Subotnick during lecture, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Morton Subotnik lecture-.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200805-07 (Image-file cd05-07)
  - Composer Morton Subotnick during lecture, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Subotnik.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200805-08 (Image-file cd05-08)
- Miller Puckette, June 2008, VI.; 1 CD-ROM (8 image files in TIFF format)
  - Composer Miller Puckette, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Miller Puckette 001.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200806-01 (Image-file cd06-01)
  - Composer Miller Puckette, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Miller Puckette 002.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200806-02 (Image-file cd06-02)
  - Composer Miller Puckette, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Miller Puckette 003.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200806-03 (Image-file cd06-03)
  - Composer Miller Puckette, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Miller Puckette 004.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200806-04 (Image-file cd06-04)
  - Composer Miller Puckette, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Miller Puckette 005.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200806-05 (Image-file cd06-05)
  - Composer Miller Puckette, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Miller Puckette 006.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200806-06 (Image-file cd06-06)
  - Composer Miller Puckette, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Miller Puckette 007.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200806-07 (Image-file cd06-07)
  - Composer Miller Puckette, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Miller Puckette 008.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200806-08 (Image-file cd06-08)
- Ben Thigpen, June 2008, VII.; 1 CD-ROM (12 image files in TIFF format)
  - Composer Ben Thigpen, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: --Ben Thigpen.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200807-01 (Image-file cd07-01)
  - Composer Ben Thigpen at audio control console, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Ben Thigpen at the control board.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200807-02 (Image-file cd07-02)
  - Composer Ben Thigpen, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Ben Thigpen composer.tif--.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200807-03 (Image-file cd07-03)
  - Composer Ben Thigpen in masterclass with student composers, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Ben Thigpen masterclass student composers.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200807-04 (Image-file cd07-04)
  - Composer Ben Thigpen, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Ben Thigpen-==composer.tif (Image-file cd07-05)
  - Composer Ben Thigpen at audio control console, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: JIB 08 047.jpg (Image-file cd07-06)
  - Composer Ben Thigpen at audio control console, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: JIB 08 047.tif (Image-file cd07-07)
  - Composer Ben Thigpen at audio control console, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: JIB 08 047====.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200807-08 (Image-file cd07-08)
  - Composer Ben Thigpen in masterclass with student composers, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: June in Buffalo 09 073.jpg (Image-file cd07-09)
  - Composer Ben Thigpen in masterclass with student composers, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: June in Buffalo 09 073.tif (Image-file cd07-10)
  - Composer Ben Thigpen in masterclass with student composers, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: masterclass with Ben Thigpen and student composers.jpg (Image-file cd07-11)
  - Composer Ben Thigpen in masterclass with student composers, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: masterclass with Ben Thigpen and student composers.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200807-12 (Image-file cd07-12)
- Charles Dodge, June 2008, VIII.; 1 CD-ROM (16 image files in TIFF format)
  - Composer Charles Dodge with conductor James Avery, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Charles Dodge James Avery.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200808-01 (Image-file cd08-01)
  - Composer Charles Dodge with conductor James Avery, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Charles Dodge James Avery.tif--.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200808-02 (Image-file cd08-02)
  - Composers Charles Dodge and Miller Puckette, with bass Nicholas Isherwood, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Charles Dodge Miller Puckette +.........tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200808-03 (Image-file cd08-03)
  - Composers Charles Dodge, Morton Subotnick, and Cort Lippe, with conductor James Avery, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Charles Dodge Morton Subotnik James Avery Corte Lippe.tif--.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200808-04 (Image-file cd08-04)
  - Composer Charles Dodge, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Charles Dodge composer-.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200808-05 (Image-file cd08-05)
  - Composer Charles Dodge at audio control console, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Charles Dodge composer....tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200808-06 (Image-file cd08-06)
  - Composer Charles Dodge, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Charles Dodge composer.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200808-07 (Image-file cd08-07)
  - Composer Charles Dodge during lecture, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Charles Dodge lecture.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200808-08 (Image-file cd08-08)
  - Composer Charles Dodge looking over score, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: composer Charles Dodge..tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200808-09 (Image-file cd08-09)
  - Composer Charles Dodge at audio control console, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: composer Charles Dodge.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200808-10 (Image-file cd08-10)
  - Composer Charles Dodge with violinist Stefan Haussler, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: composer Charles Dodge Stefan Haussler violin.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200808-11 (Image-file cd08-11)
  - Composer Charles Dodge with James Avery at the piano, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: James Avery Charles Dodge composer.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200808-12 (Image-file cd08-12)
  - Composer Charles Dodge writing musical examples during lecture, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: JIB 08 052.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200808-13 (Image-file cd08-13)
  - Composer Charles Dodge writing musical examples during lecture, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: JIB 08 053.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200808-14 (Image-file cd08-14)
  - Composer Charles Dodge writing musical examples during lecture, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: JIB 08 054.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200808-15 (Image-file cd08-15)
  - Composer Charles Dodge with violinist Stefan Haussler, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: June in Buffalo Charles Dodge Stefan Haussler violin.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200808-16 (Image-file cd08-16)
- James Avery, June 2008, IX.; 1 CD-ROM (42 image files in TIFF format)
  - Pianist Eun Ju Kim, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Eun Ju Kim.tif (Image-file cd09-01)
  - James Avery conducting rehearsal of Roberto Morales's work, Remembrance, with Eun Ju Kim, piano, Martina Roth, flute, Sven Kestel, double bass, Tom Kolor (left) and Pascal Pons (right), percussion, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: ---James Avery.tif (Image-file cd09-02)
  - Composer Charles Dodge talking with conductor James Avery, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Charles Dodge James Avery.tif (Image-file cd09-03)
  - Composer Charles Dodge with conductor James Avery, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Charles Dodge James Avery.tif--.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200809-04 (Image-file cd09-04)
  - Composers Charles Dodge, Morton Subotnick, and Cort Lippe (right), with conductor James Avery, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Charles Dodge Morton Subotnik James Avery Corte Lippe.tif--.tif (Image-file cd09-05)
  - Composer Charles Dodge with violinist Stefan Haussler, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: composer Charles Dodge Stefan Haussler violin.tif (Image-file cd09-06)
  - Pianist Eun Ju Kim rehearsing Roberto Morales's work, Remembrance, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Eun Ju Kim, piano inRemembrence by Morales.tif (Image-file cd09-07)
  - Pianist Eun Ju Kim, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Eun Ju Kim, piano.tif (Image-file cd09-08)
  - Pianist Eun Ju Kim with composer Roberto Morales, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Eun Ju Kim- Roberto Morales composer.tif (Image-file cd09-09)
  - Pianist Eun Ju Kim, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Eun Ju Piano.tif (Image-file cd09-10)
  - Pianist Eun Ju Kim, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Eun Ju.tif (Image-file cd09-11)
  - Pianist James Avery with percussionist Pascal Pons rehearsing G. Douglas Barrett's work, Derivation X, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: G. Douglas Barrett composer James Avery piano percussion Pasc.tif (Image-file cd09-12)
  - James Avery conducting rehearsal of Roberto Morales's work, Remembrance, with Eun Ju Kim, piano, Martina Roth, flute, Sven Kestel, double bass, Tom Kolor (left) and Pascal Pons (right), percussion, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: JAMES AVERY conducting.tif (Image-file cd09-13)
  - James Avery at the piano with composer Charles Dodge, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: James Avery Charles Dodge composer.tif (Image-file cd09-14)
  - James Avery at the piano, with composer G. Douglas Barrett and percussionist Pascal Pons, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: James Avery G.tif (Image-file cd09-15)
  - James Avery at the piano, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: James Avery pianist conductor.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200809-16 (Image-file cd09-16)
  - James Avery at the piano with student composer Tsai-Yun Huang, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: James Avery piano.tif (Image-file cd09-17)
  - Conductor James Avery with composer Roberto Morales, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: James Avery, composer Roberto Morales--.tif (Image-file cd09-18)
  - Conductor James Avery with composer Roberto Morales, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: James Avery, composer Roberto Morales.tif (Image-file cd09-19)
  - Pianist James Avery with percussionist Pascal Pons rehearsing G. Douglas Barrett's work, Derivation X, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: James Avery, piano Pascal Pons, percusssion.tif (Image-file cd09-20)
  - Conductor James Avery onstage with composer Roberto Morales, with musical ensemble after performance of Morales's work, Remembrance, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: JIB 08 019.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200809-21 (Image-file cd09-21)
  - Conductor James Avery onstage with composer Roberto Morales, with musical ensemble after performance of Morales's work, Remembrance, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: JIB 08 021.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200809-22 (Image-file cd09-22)
  - James Avery at the piano with student composer Tsai-Yun Huang, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: JIB 08 050.tif (Image-file cd09-23)
  - Violinist Stefan Haussler, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: June in Buffalo 09 052.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200809-24 (Image-file cd09-24)
  - Composer Roberto Morales, with conductor James Avery and pianist Eun Ju Kim, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: June in Buffalo 09 092.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200809-25 (Image-file cd09-25)
  - Composer Charles Dodge looking over score with violinist Stefan Haussler, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: June in Buffalo Charles Dodge Stefan Haussler violin.tif (Image-file cd09-26)
  - Flutist Martina Roth, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Martina Roth.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200809-27 (Image-file cd09-27)
  - Composers Cort Lippe and Roberto Morales with conductor James Avery, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Morales James Avery Cort Lippe.tif (Image-file cd09-28)
  - Pianist Eun Ju Kim with double bassist Sven Kestel and percussionist Tom Kolor rehearsing Roberto Morales's work, Remembrance, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: music by Roberto Morales Eun Ju piano.tif (Image-file cd09-29)
  - Pianist Eun Ju Kim with double bassist Sven Kestel and percussionist Tom Kolor rehearsing Roberto Morales's work, Remembrance, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: music by Roberto Morales Eun Ju piano==.tif (Image-file cd09-30)
  - Percussionist Tom Kolor, pianist Eun Ju Kim, percussionist Pascal Pons, flutist Martina Roth, and double bassist Sven Kestel rehearsing Roberto Morales's work, Remembrance (conductor James Avery just visible), June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Rehearsal for Remembrence by Morales.tif (Image-file cd09-31)
  - Pianist Eun Ju Kim and percussionist Tom Kolor rehearsing Roberto Morales's work, Remembrance, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: rehearsal Roberto Morales.tif (Image-file cd09-32)
  - James Avery conducting rehearsal of Roberto Morales's work, Remembrance, with Pascal Pons, percussion, Eun Ju Kim, piano, Martina Roth, flute, Tom Kolor, percussion, and Sven Kestel, double bass, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Remembrence by Morales-rehearsal.tif (Image-file cd09-33)
  - James Avery conducting rehearsal of Roberto Morales's work, Remembrance, with Pascal Pons, percussion, Eun Ju Kim, piano, Martina Roth, flute, Tom Kolor, percussion, and Sven Kestel, double bass, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: REMEMBRENCE rehearsal 08.tif (Image-file cd09-34)
  - James Avery conducting rehearsal of Roberto Morales's work, Remembrance, with Pascal Pons, percussion, Eun Ju Kim, piano, Martina Roth, flute, Tom Kolor, percussion, and Sven Kestel, double bass, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: REMEMBRENCE rehearsal ==.tif (Image-file cd09-35)
  - Conductor James Avery with composer Roberto Morales, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Robert Morales composer-James Avery conductor.tif (Image-file cd09-36)
  - Composer Roberto Morales and conductor James Avery examining score, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Roberto Morales James Avery==.tif (Image-file cd09-37)
  - James Avery conducting rehearsal of Roberto Morales's work, Remembrance, with Pascal Pons, percussion, Eun Ju Kim, piano, Martina Roth, flute, Tom Kolor, percussion, and Sven Kestel, double bass, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Roberto Morales REMEMBRENCE 08.tif (Image-file cd09-38)
  - James Avery conducting rehearsal of Roberto Moraless work, Remembrance, with Pascal Pons, percussion, Eun Ju Kim, piano, Martina Roth, flute, Tom Kolor, percussion, and Sven Kestel, double bass, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Roberto Morales Remembrence rehearsal-.tif (Image-file cd09-39)
  - James Avery conducting rehearsal of Roberto Morales's work, Remembrance, with Sven Kestel, double bass, Tom Kolor, percussion, Eun Ju Kim, piano, Martina Roth, flute, and Pascal Pons, percussion, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Roberto Morales rehearsal.tif (Image-file cd09-40)
  - Percussionist Pascal Pons with student composer Jonathan Wilkes, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: student composer Jonathan Wilkes percussion Pascal Pons.tif (Image-file cd09-41)
  - Percussionist Pascal Pons with student composer Jonathan Wilkes, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Wilkes composer.tifpercussion......tif (Image-file cd09-42)
- Ensemble for Intuitive Music, June 2008, X.; 1 CD-ROM (36 image files in TIFF format)
  - Daniel Hoffmann playing muted trumpet, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Daniel Hoffman ensemble f.int.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200810-01 (Image-file cd10-01)
  - Daniel Hoffmann playing muted trumpet, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Daniel Hoffman.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200810-02 (Image-file cd10-02)
  - Ensemble for Intuitive Music: Michael van Hintzenstern, piano, Daniel Hoffmann, fluegelhorn, Matthias von Hintzenstern, violoncello, and Hans Tutschku, electronics, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Ensemble for Intuitive Music 012tifTIF.tif (Image-file cd10-03)
  - Ensemble for Intuitive Music: Michael van Hintzenstern, piano, Daniel Hoffmann, fluegelhorn, Matthias von Hintzenstern, violoncello, and Hans Tutschku, electronics, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Ensemble for Intuitive Music 013.tifTIF.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200810-04 (Image-file cd10-04)
  - Ensemble for Intuitive Music: Michael van Hintzenstern, piano, Daniel Hoffmann, trumpet, Matthias von Hintzenstern, violoncello, and Hans Tutschku, electronics, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Ensemble for Intuitive Music 017.tifTIF.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200810-05 (Image-file cd10-05)
  - Violoncellist Matthias von Hintzenstern, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Ensemble for Intuitive Music 018.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200810-06 (Image-file cd10-06)
  - Violoncellist Matthias von Hintzenstern, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Ensemble for Intuitive Music 018xx.tif (Image-file cd10-07)
  - Ensemble for Intuitive Music: Michael van Hintzenstern, piano, Daniel Hoffmann, fluegelhorn, Matthias von Hintzenstern, violoncello, and Hans Tutschku, electronics, June 2008, 1 digital image (tiff format); Original file name: Ensemble for Intuitive Music 024.tifTIF.tif In UBdigit as file name: JIB200810-08 (Image-file cd10-08)